The world of Beyonders.
Humanity through consuming potions
harnessed various Beyonder abilities,
completing their promotion to life's natural order.
These twenty-two paths of advancement
start from Sequence 9.
The lower the Sequence number,
the greater the Beyonder abilities.
High-Sequence Beyonders
can possess power comparable to gods.
This path of evolution is called
the Path of the Divine.
Leave!
The evil descended body can't stand the provokation of the Saint's ashes!
It's about to be born!
Can't hold her anymore,
Captain!
Megose mutated,
the evil descended body will be born very soon!
[In Hermes]
As if in a weary dream,
You want to kill my child!
She's gone!
[In Hermes]
Illusion.
Leonard!
Blood Vessel Thief!
It suits me.
No good,
she's too fast!
I can't lock on.
Do everything you can to lead her to the memorial hall,
that's our only chance!
[In Hermes]
I pray for the power of the Evernight.
I pray for the power of the crimson.
[In Hermes]
I pray for the Goddess' loving grace.
I pray for you to let this evil descended body and "His" vessel slow to a crawl!
[In Hermes]
Submit!
Steal!
Don't think of harming my child!
I'll go seal "Him" first.
After ten seconds,
you two come out again.
Captain!
Silently count to ten.
That's an order.
You don't need to worry.
We are guarding Tingen.
They all...
are fighting side by side with me.
Ten.
I just want to keep this child!
Nine.
Why?
Must you force me?
Six.
[In Hermes]
As if in a weary dream,
caught between the other shore and the grave!
Five.
Four.
Three!
You have to die!
One!
[In Hermes]
Light!
It's over!
[In Hermes]
Submit!
Leave!
Quickly leave!
Faster!
Leave this place!
Hold on!
You―—
Evernight HQ?
You're finally here!
Old man...
Leonard!
Nightmare.
A chance!
This is...
What's going on?
To be honest...
as much as I hate other people who become Beyonders,
I respect the Nighthawks just as much.
Must not...
let "Him" be born...
absolutely...
must not..!
Captain...
[In Hermes]
Nightmare.
Klein.
[In Hermes]
Light!
Captain!
We...
We did it!
We did it.
Klein.
We...
saved Tingen.
Daly...
Captain!
Captain...
Who...
is it?
I've finally come out.
My long-awaited freedom!
Ince Zangwill,
the mortal who invited me out of Chanis Gate.
He longed to obtain
Saint Selena's ashes in Tingen.
The mortals that beg to me
always have some shameful little desires.
This is no big deal.
After a dark divination,
survivor Klein Moretti under the influence of the Antigonus Family's Notebook,
sent it to Ray Bieber's house.
This is a logically consistent coincidence.
Afterwards,
Klein shot himself.
The baffling thing is,
Klein did not die
and successfully survived,
and even joined the Nighthawks.
Interesting.
Klein's unexpectedly survived
and even killed a Sequence 7 member of the Secret Order.
Ince was enraged.
Fortunately, the results did not deviate from expectations.
Dunn Smith's spirituality
suffered severe injuries.
Of course,
as early as the ritual for the True Creator's descent,
this deity
saw through the coincidences of these events.
But,
since "He" wished to break through "His" shackles,
"He" didn't refuse.
Ah, it’s seriously unbelievable!
Klein Moretti noticed Ince Zangwill's secret influence.
He even helped Dunn
master the acting method.
No,
Ince could not believe it.
He changed his original plans.
The self-blaming Dunn
consumed Kenley's Beyonder characteristic as he usually did.
His acting and digestion procedure
were interrupted.
At the crucial moment,
he made the wrong judgement.
Taking Saint Selena's ashes
out of Chanis Gate.
Ince Zangwill killed Klein Moretti, the fellow who kept disrupting his plans.
He set up a ritual with the remaining half of the characteristic of Death’s descendant.
He consumed Saint Selena’s ashes
and successfully advanced from Sequence 5 of the Death Pathway, Gatekeeper,
to Sequence 4 of the Evernight Pathway, Nightwatcher.
Becoming
a Demigod.
The sun continued to shine brilliantly on the land.
Almost no one in Tingen City realized
how they narrowly escaped a huge disaster.
Tingen's story
ends here.
Captain and Klein...
An unencrypted telegram.
It was sent over by the Holy Cathedral.
HQ already knows who the real murderer is.
The Red Gloves are in pursuit.
...applying for the Red Gloves,
what do I need?
I asked around about it,
they said a vicious criminal snuck into Tingen.
But luckily,
the police department already stopped the crisis.
Goddess bless.
So that's why this morning Klein seemed dazed
and under a lot of pressure.
Klein is a history consultant at the police department,
his responsiblity isn't arresting criminals.
No wonder our ever-frugal Melissa was unexpectedly willing to buy five soli tickets.
It turns out you wanted Klein to relax and be happy!
Klein,
you're ba―—
The full-faced crimson moon rises,
casting light on the land.
The flame of life is fleeting,
At last, the body returns to dust.
The soul of a hero is eternal,
An unfading light,
A thorn that cuts through calamity,
A requiem sung for the wicked.
May the untamed wind
guide you to the Goddess’ divine realm.
May the stars shine in the long night.
May you return to your original purity.
The only escape is tranquility.
The only escape
is tranquility.
I'm sorry.
I failed to arrive in time.
But the person behind the scenes,
I should know who it is now.
Hornacis...
I guess this is considered a burial object?
Right now...
what am I?
Perhaps...
I’m just an evil spirit that's clawed its way
back from hell to seek revenge...
Ince
Zangwill!
Those coincidences
were the power of Sealed Artifact 0-08!
Events that are written down are bound to happen...
No.
There must be certain restrictions...
Ince's goal was to obtain Saint Selena's ashes.
Then his real target wasn't me,
but...
the Captain.
The city where Ince Zangwill currently is.
Lanevus’s location.
My opportunities of becoming powerful.
Backlund!
We...
saved Tingen.
Seville Chrysanthemum.
Symbolizes happiness!
Familiar streets, people come and go,
Forgive me this time for hurriedly leaving so,
How many skins must I shed in the end?
So my wishes stop turning into empty thoughts?
Light,
piercing through delusion.
I trust you’ve been well!
Can’t shrug off
this half-worn disguise,
Another me,
Here in name, but gone.
Don't alarm!
You'll get there!
Don’t stop!
Bloom on then,
Sunward flower.
Do you remember me, ah?
Will you remember me, ah?
Mister,
may I ask who you...
Sherlock
Moriarty.