Q Theatre
Buying Canes
Which cane do you want to buy?
A bit heavier,
a bit harder.
Silver-inlaid,
driftwood.
As hard as steel.
Seven soli and sixpence.
What about this one?
Silver-inlaid,
walnut wood.
Ten soli and threepence.
This one?
Can you even afford it? You're just asking―—
What kind of person
would carry so many golden pounds on them?
Sir,
take a look at this
gold-inlaid masterpiece.
Subtle and elegant,
for one gold pound.
For esteemed customers such as yourself,
you can enjoy our diamond membership discount right now.
Any purchase,
20% off store-wide!
Very good.
Then I'll have―—
―—this one.
Silver-inlaid driftwood,
seven soli and sixpence.
With 20% off, it comes to exactly six soli.
Fourteen soli in change,
thank you.
No discount!