Q Theatre
Klein's Nightmare
Bitter bamboo shoot soup with pork slices.
I can only taste it in my dreams!
Who's there?
Is this your acting method for Nightmare,
Captain?
Please don’t go around scaring people in dreams, okay?
I'll pretend I don't notice!
There's no taste.
Was it completely devoured?
So this is the power of Nightmare.
So Captain's goal was...
to prevent me from eating a midnight snack in my dream?!
This really is a nightmare!
Daly,
I haven't forgotten the red wine and banquet you mentioned last time.
I'm waiting until you return to Tingen.
Don't worry,
recently my potion digestion has been going very smoothly.
I've already found a very effective acting method for Nightmare.
Captain!
You can't just keep picking on only me, huh?!