The world of Beyonders.
Humanity through consuming potions
harnessed various Beyonder abilities,
completing their promotion to life's natural order.
These twenty-two paths of advancement
start from Sequence 9.
The lower the Sequence number,
the greater the Beyonder abilities.
High-Sequence Beyonders
can possess power comparable to gods.
This path of evolution is called
the Path of the Divine.
Klein,
You're here!
Mr. Neil.
Aren't the invoices this time a little too much?
How's it too much?
There are just six!
Go!
What?
The dirt on your shoes,
hurry up and throw that out!
Then it'd be better to just call it
the Society for the Protection of Fantastic Organisms!
Klein,
there's a letter for you.
by the time you see this letter
I'll have already boarded the train
to Backlund.
The Inverted Maesoleum you mentioned last time
feels familiar to me,
but it's a pity
that I can't remember any more.
So,
I intend to take a look around elsewhere.
To see if I can find more memories.
On the other hand,
the person behind the curtain has made no moves.
My leaving Tingen
perhaps can make them loosen up.
Mr. Azik has left too.
What do we do from here on out?
If the black hand behind the curtain moves again,
relying on just myself...
This is...
What are you doing?
Captain.
This wanted order is―—
Did I not warn you?
Then that's my oversight.
This is an archbishop
that lost control three years ago.
He took Sealed Artifact 0-08 and vanished.
To this day he has yet to be discovered.
The Holy Church's order
is if you discover him, don't alert him and immediately make a report.
Otherwise,
you'll one thousand percent
die in the line of duty.
Sealed Artifact 0-08 is...
A Grade 0 Sealed Artifact.
The highest danger grade.
The highest confidentiality.
Not to be inquired about.
Not to be disseminated.
Not to be described.
Not to be spied upon.
Regarding 0-08,
all I know is that it looks like a common quill pen.
It doesn't require ink to write.
Pen?
After a Beyonder loses control and dies,
they will leave behind things that are rich with Beyonder powers.
If they cannot be controlled,
they have to be sealed.
This is one of the origins of Sealed Artifacts.
Then what if
they are controllable?
You wouldn't want to know the answer.
Whether it's a Nighthawk
or a Mandated Punisher,
Machinery Hivemind;
they all will face losing control
or sacrifice during a mission.
Klein,
you have to get used to it.
Pull yourself together.
I understand.
Captain.
The Captain is right.
I should pull myself together.
There's still a black hand behind the curtain to investigate.
I still need to
go home.
Klein,
I happened to buy some
sweet iced tea.
You liked this,
right?
Thank you.
Captain.
The things you applied for earlier
came in today too.
Tarot cards.
A total of twenty-two cards.
The card faces are inlaid with pure silver and other metal threads.
Only has a restrictive effect on undead creatures.
Why'd you suddenly think to use tarot cards as a weapon?
Cards are more covert than guns.
A weapon that's not like a weapon.
Only at the critical moment can you
deliver a fatal counter-attack.
The power is sufficient.
The accuracy is lacking a bit.
No need to rush.
From now on, I'll teach you combat and techniques for delivering force.
Anything else you don't understand
you can also ask me directly.
You're already Sequence 8.
You should have more
knowledge about contact with the spiritual world.
I've found a teacher for you.
Tonight at around 10 o'clock they'll come find you.
A Sequence 6 Spirit Guide.
Don't go to bed early.
You're back, Klein.
Have you had dinner?
I already ate,
Melissa.
What's up.
Right now you look like
you're in better spirits.
Sorry.
I made you worry.
Right!
This.
I recently transitioned to a full-time role in the police department.
So...
You got another raise!
As expected, knowledge is wealth.
Basic Accounting Theory?
Benson,
this is...
I really don't hope in another five years
that I'll still be making less than two pounds a week.
It only looks very hypnotic.
First study basic mathematical logic and relevant legal knowledge,
it's helpful for studying accounting.
Really.
Without a doubt.
Okay.
I'll work hard
to study.
That's the biggest difference between humans and curly-haired baboons!
This copper whistle was something I had with me when I woke up.
It can summon my messenger.
Find a relatively safe place,
use some force and give it a blow,
and the little guy will come out quickly.
Messenger...
No sound.
It's broken.
What's going on?
It's them.
Mr. Azik.
You call this a little guy?
Madam Daly!
I thought I'd be able to give you a big scare.
Just recently that messenger ulted from the get-go.
Madam, what you did just now can only be considered a basic attack.
As expected, you are the Spirit Guide.
Madam Daly!
Congratulations on your promotion to Sequence 6.
I still prefer the name Spirit Medium.
Today, I'll first teach you two Beyonder abilities.
Summoning a messenger,
and a different mediumship ritual.
Using ritualistic magic,
you can enter another person's Mind World,
and explore memories hidden deep in the subconscious.
Usually,
the existence of the human will
resists unprotected communication between souls.
So it can be quite troublesome.
There are also quite a few
dangers.
In the Mind World,
everything...
Madam.
Will today's knowledge be
a bit too much?
Captain!
You're here to see Madam Daly, right?
Don't mind him.
Entering peoples' dreams to scare them again.
Sorry, Daly.
I interrupted your lesson.
Remember you promised me
red wine and a banquet.
Klein.
Bring your weapons,
there's an urgent mission.
Hood Eugen.
He's been disguised as an ordinary citizen of Tingen.
Recently,
he suddenly went mad.
A suspected Sequence 7 Psychiatrist
who accidentally exposed his Beyonder abilities.
His dreams are already a sea of chaos.
It's no longer possible to conduct an interrogation with Nightmare.
You try using a mediumship ritual.
Psychiatrists are part of the Spectator Pathway.
They have strong psychological defense mechanisms.
Exercise caution.
Have you slept?
I haven't.
I've been
waiting for you.
You knew I was coming.
You said you'd bring me a cake.
I never promised you that.
El.
El said.
He'd give me cake if I didn't sleep at night.
He didn't.
There's no cake.
It's you.
You stole my cake!
Don't get so worked up.
Nightmare.
The Captain's Nightmare ability has been enhanced.
It looks like the potion digestion has been going smoothly these past few days.
Let's start,
Klein.
I pray for the power of the Evernight.
I pray for the power of the mysterious.
I pray for the Goddess' loving grace.
I pray that you'll
allow me to communicate with Hood Eugen's spirituality.
So light.
Yet so heavy.
What sound is this?
This is the Spirit World Madam Daly spoke of.
Overlapping with the real world.
The past, present, and future converge here.
Innumerable information flows here.
This leads to the entrance of Hood Eugen's Mind World.
Tell me.
Who are you.
What organization are you from?
Hood Eugen.
Psychology
Alchemists.
Psychology Alchemists!
Psychology Alchemists.
What is their purpose in coming to Tingen?
No response.
Did I ask the wrong question,
or
is Eugen also unsure?
Then who is El?
El.
Lanevus.
Lanevus!
Eugen remembers his cake even he's he's gone mad.
The two must have a close relationship.
That criminal who cheated both money and sex.
It's very likely that he's also a Beyonder.
Swindler.
Could it be he's what the files referred to as
a Marauder Pathway Sequence 8—
—Swindler?
Why did Lanevus come looking for you?
He said.
You should be able to see!
What the presence is behind me.
And in some sense, the Psychology Alchemists
definitely also have a connection to "Him",
provided you only offer a little bit of help!
You'll not only harness the power of the potion,
but also the method to avoid losing control!
You'll also get the divinity that Beyonders have always dreamed of.
Immortal divinity!
Hood Eugen.
So long as you can seize the opportunity
we can also become the rulers of this world!
What's the meaning of this?
A Swindler's characteristic style of speaking!
What kind of help
does Lanevus want you to provide?
Help...
I provided help...
I provided help!
I let...
Eugen's spiritual sea has already collapsed.
If I don't escape quickly...
Shit!
What happened?
You almost got lost in his Mind World.
Captain.
I saw a gloomy altar.
And a shadow resembling the True Creator.
No wonder Eugen immediately lost control.
A gloomy altar.
If it's related to the True Creator
then it's very likely also related to the Aurora Order.
And the Psychology Alchemists
may also be hidden behind it,
tacitly allowing these events to unfold.
Aurora Order.
Captain.
Do you still remember that letter written to Mr. Z?
The letter Aurora Order member Sirius carried.
He mentioned in the letter
that he was waiting for an appropriate opportunity,
at the arrival of the end of days,
to offer his so-called God
all the lambs in Tingen.
I think this is something that Lanevus planned.
There's a deep connection.
This situation may be rather serious.
We must re-investigate Lanevus.
Member of Parliament Mrs. Maynard bellowed,
"You shameless bitch."
You shameless bitch!
She's the murderer!
Why are you not arresting her?!
Madam Sharon.
A famous socialite in Tingen.
Baron Khoy's widow.
These people are all members of the Conservative Party and the New Party.
They have a close relationship
with Madam Sharon.
Beside her is the incumbent Baron Khoy.
Madam Sharon's stepson.
Stepson?
I'm going to sue her!
I'm going to sue you police for dereliction of duty!
These kinds of slutty whores
deserve to be punished with a pear of anguish!
Mrs. Member of Parliament.
Your vulgar words are unbecoming of your position.
I sent Madam Sharon to meet with Member of Parliament Maynard last night.
Do you
have any problems with me?
As expected of Tingen's most famous socialite.
Let's go upstairs and take a look.
John Maynard.
New Party member.
Tingen Member of Parliament,
mayoral candidate.
The initial autopsy report shows
that the time of death was between nine and eleven last night.
The corpse has not been moved.
The butler discovered it this morning.
Madam Sharon was the last person the Member of Parliament met while he was alive.
Ruling out the influence of supernatural factors,
and also ruling out foul play,
the initial verdict is death due to sudden illness.
What did you find?
Unanimous with Frye.
But I think
the death of this Member of Parliament is not so simple.
It's definitely related to supernatural factors.
When I was searching for clues related to the Lanevus case,
I discovered that Lanevus leased the South Borough Steel Factory.
There's a hidden exchange of interests behind this.
The one really in charge
is a highly respected Member of Parliament.
Mayoral candidate,
John Maynard.
He's the one I was going to focus today's investigation on.
The time of death is too coincidental.
Investigate deeper into Madam Sharon's social network.
See if she has any connections to Lanevus.
The death of John Maynard.
The existence of supernatural influences.
They exist!
As expected.
Our investigation was interfered with.
Madam Sharon is a Beyonder.
Madam Sharon and Lanevus are connected.
I can't divine it.
She's using a pseudonym.
Or.
She's a very powerful Beyonder.
There's not enough genuine information.
There's no way to verify anything else either.
How many times have I been interfered with now?
It's too coincidental, isn't it?
Could it be that
Madam Sharon is related to the black hand behind the curtain?
Burn my broken shell to new sight
To be free in mist to hold a cup of light
Where are the flames that come in fury?
Where are the keys that carve truth from me?
Into the dark to dream and scream my name
Wonder or dismay
Madness or Decay
With fragile light
I vow to guard a world I stay
Stiring or delay
Rebirth or be same
With whispers in grey
Guide my shadow way
Fade away
O Magnificent Deity,
I am willing to dedicate my life to you.
This is...
a new prayer.
Mr. Fool.
I have some good news to share.
Your aforementioned
Higher Exam for selecting talent through public examinations,
has already obtained the approval of both the King and the Prime Minister.
Early next year, it's projected
to enter the official implementation phase.
So fast.
It seems that Miss Justice's family
has quite a bit of political influence.
Very good.
Honorable Mr. Fool.
I also have a matter I'd like to consult you about.
The Aurora Order has continuously been pursuing the holy residence of the True Creator.
Whether
it is the legendary Forsaken Land of the Gods.
Forsaken Land of the Gods.
It's related to the True Creator.
What was Emperor Roselle looking for in the Forsaken Land of the Gods?
This is not something you should know now.
Please forgive me for overstepping my boundaries.
You may continue.
Miss Justice.
I would like to ask you for a favor.
What kind of favor?
In Backlund,
find the whereabouts of a person.
This matter
is high-risk.
But to this end I will pay you the compensation you deserve.
May I ask who to look for?
One of the Seven Pirate Admirals,
Vice Admiral Hurricane
Qilangos.
Seven Pirate Admirals.
Speaking of which,
he also went to Backlund.
Mr. Fool.
Could it be that he's performing a miracle?
O Magnificent Deity.
I am willing to use my blood to please you.
What language is this?
The root language of Loenese, Ancient Feysac!
Not exactly.
Please allow us, the People of the Dark, be freed from the curse of our destiny.
It seems to be
Jotun!
O Magnificent Deity.
Please bestow the sun and light once more upon this land that you have forsaken.
It really is Jotun!
Fortunately I've learned a bit.
Where in the world is Jotun still used?
This is an ancient antique that is thousands of years old.
Magnificient Deity.
A land that was forsaken.
Forsaken Land of the Gods.
You—
Your Grace,
are you God?
I am not God.
I am merely someone
interested in the long history of this world,
The Fool.
Justice.
The Hanged Man.
Choose a card, then.
It will serve as your codename.
I choose
The Sun!
我
才刚来
还不太了解愚者先生
但是
愚者先生敢无视黑暗深处那些恐怖怪物
将我从诅咒之地拉止来
一定无所不能
勇敢无畏
不会
真的闹鬼吧
我心中的愚者先生
自然是强大
比肩神明的强大
我只有序列八
你不要过来啊
我要先道歉
我总是想用金钱来做交易补偿
愚者先生这样的大人物
怎么可能看得上庸俗的金钱
总之
愚者先生在我心中
就是一位超凡脱俗
睿智沉稳的长者
看什么呢
这么专注
你说
小丑的平衡能力和猫比
哪个更强