Q Theatre
Story of 1000 Pounds
Integrity comes first!
Replace the captain!
The captain should resign!
Alger.
It's payday again.
Everyone is still waiting on last last month's money.
The Church of Storms did provide the money.
But it was cut in half.
It was also skimmed off at every level.
By the time it got to my hands there wasn't much left.
Then what do we do?
Don't tell me that we grand Mandated Punishers
are really going to resort to piracy?
Don't worry.
Give me one day's time.
I'll make up all the salaries in full.
Moreover.
I'll do double!
Have you lost control,
Alger?
At the Tarot Club meeting, Miss Justice did agree to provide one thousand pounds.
But in such a short time...
can she really procure that much?
The captain is mighty!
You're amazing, captain!
I'll follow you no matter what!
Captain!
Where'd you manage to get this much money?
The captain is amazing!
It seems the Tarot Club can not only help me ascend faster to a High-Sequence Beyonder,
but it can also be my
path to wealth!
One thousand pounds in non-sequential banknotes...
I suppose Miss Justice
put in quite a bit of effort, didn't she?
My little Audrey,
you've thought of a way to resolve the government's structural chaos
and its inefficiency?
Yes, father!
Exams!
Every year
hold an exam open to the public,
and select the best officials for various government departments.
The officials
can ensure the effective operation of the kingdom.
Even if all those ministers turn into curly-haired baboons,
it won't even matter!
Truly wonderful,
my little Audrey!
To think that you could come up with proposals that even the Cabinet couldn't provide!
That's to be expected!
This is a proposal given by Mr. Fool.
It's a god's proposal!
As expected of my daughter.
You've helped Father with important business!
Father will increase your allowance.
Every month I'll add...
one thousand pounds!