The world of Beyonders.
Humanity through consuming potions
harnessed various Beyonder abilities,
completing their promotion to life's natural order.
These twenty-two paths of advancement
start from Sequence 9.
The lower the Sequence number,
the greater the Beyonder abilities.
High-Sequence Beyonders
can possess power comparable to gods.
This path of evolution is called
the Path of the Divine.
In the crimson,
Dunn Smith,
over the corpse of Kenley White...
Captain.
Captain is drinking Kenley's blood.
What's going on?
He's showing early signs of losing control!
It shouldn't be.
Captain has been acting as a Nightmare all this time.
Klein.
What's wrong.
No,
it's nothing.
I'm a little tired.
Don't let sorrow drain your spirit too much.
You have to get used to these sooner or later.
While Sharon Khoy's Spirit Body has not dissipiated yet,
you should use mediumship to investigate a bit.
I got it,
Captain.
With the Captain, it looks like
nothing is out of the ordinary.
Was that a hallucination?
That's not right.
It wasn't a hallucination.
Kenley's corpse,
it's really missing something.
Why?
Why is it like this again?
Kenley...
He was engaged just last month.
Why would you become a Beyonder?
Why is there always danger?
May the Goddess bless you.
May you find true peace.
Captain.
What exactly did you do?
Earlier you ordered me to go downstairs and handle the aftermath,
did you want to draw me away?
Kenley...
died because of 3-0217.
3-0217,
it was Captain who gave it to Kenley.
What am I thinking?
It was a logical decision back then!
But
3-0217,
it was also the Captain who suggested using it.
According to Klein's mediumship of Sharon Khoy,
the Demoness Sect appears to be collaborating with the Aurora Order,
and the Lanevus case
is related to Tingen's end of days.
Follow these clues,
examine them again carefully.
Understood.
Captain.
Now that Sharon Khoy is dead,
can the Tingen crisis
temporarily be lifted?
Sharon Khoy may be a key part of the end of days,
but the evil organizations
will never make just one move.
You're back, Klein.
Have you been busy lately?
There's breakfast in the kitchen, do you want to eat a bit?
Okay.
Wait until my work is over.
The letter's already been sent.
I hope Mr. Azik and Madam Daly can reply as soon as possible.
I'm not clear on the things that have occurred.
I also don't know what state the Captain is in.
Only you two can give me answers.
The reason for Dunn Smith's abnormality.
No response.
That means that there was insufficient information,
so the divination failed...
Generally speaking,
divination involving one's own safety
requires the least amount of information.
If I start from the aspect of divining my own safety...
Dunn Smith’s abnormality
will lead me to danger.
Positive!
Captain’s abnormality will lead me to danger!
And the danger level is significant.
Mr. Azik replied!
The scenario you described
reminded me of Vampires and Mutants.
Natural vampires were already on the brink of extinction before the dragons and giants bowed out of the stage of world history,
so already close to extinction.
But I recall
that there's a particular Pathway with some Sequence
whose potion name was called Vampire.
Regarding Mutants,
some speculate they are ordinary humans who, after being tainted or cursed,
transform into monsters under specific circumstances.
Your superior
might be a potential Mutant.
Of course,
these are all my personal guesses.
But no matter which,
it proves that your superior is in an unstable condition right now,
and very dangerous.
You'd best be careful.
Klein.
Captain.
Head to 62 Howes Street.
Leonard found Lanevus' residence.
He needs your help.
You're here.
You didn't sleep well.
How did you figure it out?
You guys found a clue from Hood Eugen
and suspected that Lanevus was connected to Sirius.
Sirius had interactions with many of the residents on Howes Street,
so I searched every one of them.
An old man looked Lanevus' picture
and felt that he looked similar to the resident at number 62,
but it's already been a long time since he's come back.
I suspect this place
has a hidden secret chamber.
The secret chamber or hidden compartment in this building.
A letter again.
Congratulations
on finally finding this letter!
This means that you’re not too stupid.
You qualify to take part in what I've designed, this
game of life and death.
Madness,
will eventually pay the price.
The crime of blasphemy―—
there is no salvation.
Poverty,
disease,
Child laborers that die before their time.
Workers who seldom live past thirty years old.
Every factory in this city
is enveloped in boundless resentment.
Our game
shall take place in this kind of setting.
Fools,
prepare yourselves!
I've placed a bomb in the middle of Tingen,
a bomb that will continue to grow stronger as time goes on!
A bomb?
Go find it then,
dear friends.
Time is tight.
We have to hurry back and tell the Captain.
If you fail the game...
boom!
The whole of Tingen
will be reduced to a ruin.
The one who enjoys giving his friends pleasant surprises,
Lanevus.
I've never heard of
a bomb that can grow stronger.
It's a bomb related to mysticism.
Such as an evil ritual that continuously accumulates power.
I agree with your guess.
The description that Lanevus wrote
might be the energy source that constantly strengthens the bomb.
The problem is
where is the bomb?
What happened?
Where's the Captain?
A bomb?
Could it be atop the altar in Hood Eugen's Mind World?
But where's the altar?
Under the center of Tingen...
Hello.
Miss Megose!
Lanevus's fiancee.
Before she had some issues with her mental health.
She says her child sings in her stomach and also whistles.
Miss Megose.
What brings you here?
I don't know why,
I suddenly thought of coming to Zouteland Street
and suddenly thought of coming up to take a look.
Her mental health seems to have worsened...
Last time I didn't have time to activate Spirit Vision.
Don't look!
If you look,
you'll die!
The bomb that Lanevus set isn't on the altar...
it's the sinister existence that's in Megose's body!
I started the Industrial Revolution with my own hands
and personally ushered in the Age of Steam and Machinery,
but will this only become the hotbed for the descent
of an Evil God upon this world?!
The copper whistle is being supressed!
The Flaring Sun Charm is not affected.
Miss Megose.
Is there something you want to commission?
I want to chat
about Lanevus.
He said
you guys know a lot.
Who
is "he"?
My
child.
May I ask,
do you want coffee
or black tea?
A cup of warm water.
Please wait a moment,
Madam.
Keep her stable.
Klein.
I heard
you and Mr. Lanevus
first met at a ball.
That's right.
I
first met him
at a parliamentary ball.
He was outstanding,
elegant and wealthy,
that night he was the young entrepreneur all the girls were most interested in.
At that time there were so many beautiful girls waiting to dance with him.
But I don't know why
he only invited me.
From the waltz to the courante,
he was with me the whole night!
Every word he said made me happy.
Every expression captivated me.
At that time
I knew I never wanted to leave him in my life.
Later they told me
he's a swindler.
That he deceived me.
But it wasn't like that!
He was very good to me.
He frequently brought me to attend meetings with his friends!
He even brought me to lots of wonderful places.
That day!
That day...
He gave me a necklace.
He even said
he wanted to give me a surprise.
Descendant of Death's characteristic
and a mortal body,
to create a vessel to welcome the descent!
Boundless resentment and darkness
will be the breastmilk and honey that nourish the Blessed.
You're saying the child she's bearing is not Lanevus'.
Correct.
I attempted to activate Spirit Vision
but my spirituality warned me,
"Do not look directly at God!"
Connecting the altar in Eugen's Mind World
and the divinity Lanevus promised Eugen.
I suspect what's in Megose's stomach is
the descended body of the True Creator.
That's right.
So that's why Mr. Havre, who was tailing Megose,
would suddenly lose control.
It's possible Old Neil also suffered from "His" catalysis.
Moreover,
We only just searched Lanevus' letter
and Megose suddenly appeared at our door.
An extraordinary coincidence.
It's too obvious.
Too direct.
It’s already completely no longer hidden.
It looks like the mastermind behind the scenes has finally made a move.
But after that time,
he just disappeared.
I've looked for so long,
in so many places,
and I can't find him!
Don't be so worried,
Miss Megose.
Careful with your child.
Child!
Her mental state already can't hold on for much longer.
What about Frye and Royale?
They haven't returned yet.
Contact all non-combatants to evacuate.
Let the police department evacuate the citizens as soon as possible.
Regarding Mr. Lanevus' whereabouts,
we actually got our hands on some new clues.
Captain’s orders.
It's an emergency situation.
All civilian posts evacuate.
It's dangerous here.
Go!
The True Creator's descended body
is also Sequence 4 Demigod at minimum.
I need to ask for assistance from the Holy Cathedral immediately.
And also from the Mandated Punishers and the Machinery Hivemind.
Sequence 4 Demigod.
Relying just on us...
is there a chance of success?
Mr. Azik!
If Mr. Azik is still in Tingen
the supression on the copper whistle will weaken!
I need to quickly contact Mr. Azik.
Mr. Azik!
The mastermind behind the scenes
that made my fate disharmonious and stole the skull of your child
might have appeared!
This involves the True Creator
so the situation is desperate.
If the Holy Cathedral's reinforcements haven't arrived,
the evil descended body will be born.
Go grab two offensive Sealed Artifacts.
I'll apply to use 3-0782,
Mutated Sun Sacred Emblem.
It was already lent to Backlund yesterday.
Such a coincidence!
There are only three Grade 2 Sealed Artifacts in Tingen City at the moment.
Two of them have unknown effectiveness on High-Sequence Beyonders.
2-105, Blood Vessel Thief, is tested to be effective on High-Sequence Beyonders.
Within a specific range, it can steal
some abilities from certain targets.
But the probability is comparatively smaller.
Let's go with the Blood Vessel Thief, then.
Every person that touches 2-105
will have their life stolen.
Remember clearly,
the limit for a Sequence 8 is
half an hour.
I'll keep that in mind,
and also tell Leonard.
My dear Poet,
it’s time for you to show your true secret.
Then which one are using?
I have other plans.
Saint Selena...
I'll apply to use the core seals,
Saint Selena's ashes.
This...
requires approval from the Holy Cathedral.
As Captain of the Tingen Nighthawks,
during emergencies I have the authority to
apply for Saint Selena's ashes!
The core seals have been retrieved.
Chanis Gate is relying on you all now.
May the Goddess bless you all.
The Holy Cathedral sent back a telegram.
Stall for as much time as possible.
Strong reinforcements are coming immediately.
What about those coincidences?
No response.
Right now what we need the most is time.
Let's hope the descended body in Megose's stomach can wait.
So he has another residence on Howes Street?
He's never told me that before!
Don't be foolish!
Go!
Leave!
You!
What are you hiding?
Mr. Lanevus...
has actually been going through some difficulties,
which is why he was forced to leave Tingen.
Once it's settled,
he'll come back to find you.
And your child too.
Really?
Of course it's like this!
He really loves this child...
for this child,
he'll definitely come back!
Mr. Moretti also said before,
as long I have the child,
I can find Lanevus!
Klein Moretti?
That's right.
Mr. Outstanding Seer!
It seems like there was someone that told me
if I just came here
you guys could help me give birth to my child faster!
Who.
Who told you that?
There's just a voice...
a voice that said...
go to Zouteland Street to see some friends...
The evil descended body
can still be kept stable for the time being.
I'll go up first.
You guard here.
Captain.
I almost forgot.
The letter Daly gave you
is here with me.
She told me to explain myself to you.
In the field of mysticism,
there exists a law.
The characteristics of a Beyonder are never destroyed
and are never reduced.
It’s only passed from one carrier to the next.
When Daly and I noticed this,
the Holy Cathedral immediately made us swear an oath of secrecy
and gave us two choices.
The first was after our teammates die,
to hand over all their Beyonder characteristics to the Holy Cathedral.
The second was,
for those of the same Pathway,
to consume their bodies.
I don't know their true wishes.
At the same time,
this will substantially disturb my potion digestion.
But I still made this choice
to be with them forever.
Captain.
My child!
Go!
Little one!
Calm down,
Miss Megose!
Think of your child!
His birth
will definitely bring blessings to both his mother and father!
In a few days Lanevus will come back!
You only need to wait a few days!
Wait a few days?
Didn't you say if the child was born...
his dad would come back?!
The final curtain
rises!
Leave!
The evil descended body can't stand the provokation of the Saint's ashes!
It's about to be born!
Saint's ashes?
Burn my broken shell to new sight
To be free in mist to hold a cup of light
Where are the flames that come in fury?
Where are the keys that carve truth from me?
Into the dark to dream and scream my name
Wonder or dismay
Madness or Decay
With fragile light
I vow to guard a world I stay
Stirring or delay
Rebirth or be same
With whispers in gray
Guide my shadow way
Fade away