Q Theatre
Old Neil's Penny Pinching strategy
From a certain point of view
your marksmanship is very accurate!
You must be hungry.
Here.
So
expensive
Thank you,
So
expensive
but... I'm not hungry yet.
So
expensive
You truly are young.
All expenses during training and missions
can reasonably fall under reimbursement.
Three meals and afternoon tea are reimbursable!
Transportation expenses are reimbursable.
Clothing wear and tear is reimbursable!
Of course,
the bulk of reimbursable expenses
are in ritualistic magic and charms.
Ritualistic magic requires silverware.
Apart from charms made of silver
some are even made of gold!
However, this is just theory.
I, Old Neil, have never done such a thing.
Is that so?
Small gains you can make,
but with big ones you musn't be greedy!
Old Neil.
You reimbursed a stack of receipts just this morning.
You'll have to wait some time before coming back.
Dunn!
I'm here to be reimbursed!
Okay.
This is also acceptable?!
You still
have a lot to learn,
youngster!