The world of Beyonders.
Humanity through consuming potions
harnessed various Beyonder abilities,
completing their promotion to life's natural order.
These twenty-two paths of advancement
start from Sequence 9.
The lower the Sequence number,
the greater the Beyonder abilities.
High-Sequence Beyonders
can possess power comparable to gods.
This path of evolution is called
the Path of the Divine.
Order.
Order!
Ladies and gentlemen.
Yesterday,
former head of the Tingen New Party, Mr. John Maynard,
met with an untimely death,
and has passed on to the Berserk Sea.
I am filled with deep regret.
Punish the murderer!
Arrest Sharon Khoy!
Hang that woman!
Hang her!
Mr. Maynard
sadly passed away due to heart disease.
Any rumors
are an insult to the deceased.
We all know that
disease,
poverty,
unrest,
famine,
are all corroding Tingen.
People are unsure of what lies ahead.
They have lost faith in the future.
I hereby pledge
that I shall unite the New Party and the Conservative Party
in accordance with the late Mr. Maynard's wishes,
and implement the new policies!
The resolution on the new policies did not pass by an absolute majority!
This is being forced through!
You are flagrantly violating the Charter of Rights and Freedoms!
I will lead Tingen
down a road of light and hope.
A road to reform and revitalization.
Oppose the new policies!
I will push to establish a new order,
and let us escape this chaos.
Poverty.
Crime.
and savagery.
Establishing a free
and joyful Tingen!
Break through our shackles,
the old order
will be consigned to the past!
The old order
The future
belongs to Tingen!
The old order
will be consigned to the past!
The future
belongs to Tingen!
Very well done.
This is a reward for you.
Send me somewhere.
I did not expect that Maynard's unexpected death
would stir her to action.
Follow that carriage up ahead.
I hope everything goes smoothly on the Captain's side.
Search for any trace of Beyonders.
Take care to be discreet.
Copy that.
Understood.
Yes, Captain.
Tris.
Captain.
I've discovered something.
This can of powder
is unlike any powder I recognize.
It's mummy powder.
The latest craze in aristocratic circles.
I heard it can be brewed into a drug that satisfies both men and women.
M―—
Mummy powder has that kind of use?
Lost them.
Straight forward.
It’s been nullified.
Madam Sharon applied interference.
This place is
Blackthorn.
Why would she come around here?
Your Excellency, Saintess.
I like this captivating atmosphere.
Apathy.
Oppression.
Suffering.
Despair.
Are all an exquisite recipe for a witch.
It seems that
you are advancing very smoothly.
The core of city council is just some men.
No one
understands men more than us.
Yet no one
also understands women more than us.
Insatiable, lecherous insects.
Who wouldn't want to wash away their soul in ecstasy for one night?
Once you've tasted that all-consuming pleasure,
there's no escaping it again.
You become a shameful puppet
dancing on my strings atop the altar.
In less than two days,
I can present the whole of Tingen
to you,
my Excellency.
I really admire you,
Sharon.
But an accident like Maynard's
will disrupt my infiltration of the kingdom.
I don't want to see it again.
If you cannot exercise control over your pleasures,
then don't blame me for taking you in under my skirt another time.
I will instruct you thoroughly.
Looks like nothing's out of the ordinary.
The Captain and the others have already searched it before.
An intermediate layer.
Madam Sharon's past lover!
That's not right.
This person seems to look a bit like Madam Sharon.
Could she be the same as Instigator Tris?
Did she also receive the effects of the potion?
My little cutie.
So you were here.
Madam Sharon can detect my tailing.
I need to use a more covert method.
I remember Madam Daly said before,
The ritualistic magic for summoning a messenger
is to pray to yourself.
No need to go through a god.
Therefore, it's quite secretive.
The important part to the prayer is
the exact description of the summoning object.
Remember,
don't change the actual description of the summoning object,
or the ritual could easily attract a terrifying monster.
[In Ancient Hermes]
I!
[In Hermes]
I summon in my name.
The Fool that doesn’t belong to this era,
[In Hermes]
the mysterious ruler above the gray fog;
the King of Yellow and Black who wields good luck.
Did the summoning fail?
If I were to summon myself,
I should also need to respond to the prayer from above the gray fog.
I really summoned myself!
It also has some powers of the gray fog.
It seems
it also brought some powers of the Flaring Sun Charms.
As expected,
the sun won't burn my Spirit Body!
Demoness Sect?
Yes, Captain.
It's possible a Clown's spiritual perception is relatively strong.
I saw the statue of the Primordial Demoness.
The Primordial Demoness again.
Notify Frye to guard Chanis Gate for me.
Call Kenley.
I want to request a Sealed Artifact to restrain the Witch,
3-0217.
Application form.
Come in.
This is
the power of the seal behind Chanis Gate.
3-0217.
Spirit Medium’s Mirror.
It originally belonged to a Spirit Medium.
Do not look directly at it.
It deals bonus damage to the Witch.
Even as fragments,
it can turn them to dust.
Remember,
3-0217 cannot aimed at yourself or your teammates.
I'll drag her into a dream from a distance.
You two make haste.
Nightmare's control has strengthened.
Seal!
It went so smoothly.
Black Flame.
Mirror Substitution!
Kenley!
She's not under the control of Nightmare!
It's all an illusion.
If it wasn’t for the fact that the statue happened to be beside me,
I would be deep asleep now,
waiting for you to wake me up with a kiss.
Go to hell!
Heretic!
No!
Kenley!
There's a familiar presence.
Was it you?
Playing little tricks this afternoon.
The little mouse sneaking into my house.
Only Sequence 8.
So you were able to stay concealed from me.
You...
what secrets are you hiding?
Evernight
Slumber!
Mirror Substitution again!
Insect that overestimates his capabilities.
Seal!
Pleasure!
It cannot be destroyed.
That statue!
Icy Frost!
Why bother?
A futile struggle.
Listen
to this wonderful sound!
Your death knell
has already tolled!
This continent
will soon return to its rightful order!
Let this order
start from Tingen.
Come!
Young Nighthawk.
Speak your secrets!
To the Primordial,
swear your loyalty!
Remember,
only by following me
and advancing towards the Primordial,
can you
attain sainthood and salvation!
And avoid
the end of days.
Sleep Demon.
Pleasure!
Captain.
Very good.
The last remaining insect
has finally shown up.
You can go die together!
Hidden Form.
Illusion.
Blood Curse.
Evernight
Purification!
Too fast!
It's impossible to lock on.
I need to foresee her movements.
A chance!
No!
It's okay.
Kenley!
I...
made a mistake.
I was fooled by Madam Sharon.
I didn’t expect
her to have long escaped the dream.
May the Goddess bless you.
May you find true peace.
May the serene night
no longer harbor any danger or madness.
Captain.
I’ve finished handling the aftermath downstairs―—
苦笋肉片汤
只有在梦里才能吃到了
谁
这就是你扮演梦魔的方式吗
Yes, Captain.
拜托不要在梦里吓人好不好
假装看不见
没味道
被彻底吞食了
这就是梦魔的能力
所以队长的目的
就是让我在梦里都吃不到夜宵
真是噩梦啊
戴莉
你上次说的红酒大餐我没有忘
等你回廷根
放心
最近我魔药消化得很顺利
我已经找到了非常有效的扮演梦的方法
Yes, Captain.
你也不能尽逮着我一个人啊