Old Neil's Mysticism Classroom Episode 1
Studious Beyonders.
Old Neil's Mysticism Classroom
You all, like Klein, are promising youngsters.
Today, let's talk about the geographical distribution of the Northern Continent.
Old Neil's Mysticism Classroom
as well as the Mystical World's various language systems.
The continential mainland we inhabit
is mainly divided into Eastern, Western, Southern, and Northern continents.
Within the Northern Continent there are four major countries and several small countries.
The four major countries are the Intis Republic,
Feysac Empire,
Loen Kingdom, as well as the Feynapotter Kingdom.
The main small countries in the central-southern region are Segar,
Lenburg, and Masin.
These are the three largest among the independent cities.
Within the Loen Kingdom
is the main area of activity for the Nighthawks.
Located in the east of the Northern Continent,
with the capital: Backlund.
It is backed by Hornacis Mountain Range,
faces the Sunia Sea to the east,
and stretches south to Desi Bay
adjacent to the Berserk Sea.
The main deities worshipped are the Lord of Storms,
the Evernight Goddess, and the God of Steam and Machinery.
Pennies, soli, and gold pounds are the basic currencies in cirulation in the Loen Kingdom.
Copper pennies are the lowest tier.
Soli are the second tier
and are represented by banknotes.
Gold pounds are the top-tier currency,
also represented by banknotes,
but are backed by gold
and directly pegged to it.
The Klein family
reside in Tingen City, located in the northern part of the Loen Kingdom.
This city is known as the City of Universities.
In addition to that,
there are also countries located in the western part of the Northern Continent.
The Intis Republic,
capital city: Trier.
They worship the Church of the Eternal Blazing Sun
and the Church of the God of Steam and Machinery,
mastering the Bard, Savant, and Hunter Pathways.
The country in the northern part is the Feysac Empire.
They exclusively worships the Church of the God of Combat,
mastering the two major Hunter and Warrior Pathways.
The southern country is the Feynapotter Kingdom.
Worshipping the Church of the Earth Mother,
mastering the Arbiter, Planter, and Apothecary Pathways.
In our world,
the main languages include Loenese, Ancient Hermes, and Hermes, among others.
Different languages are used not only for daily communication
but also carry specific functions and symbolic meanings.
Loenese is the most widely used language in the Loen Kingdom.
The Seer Pathway I follow is written like this in Loenese.
Ancient Hermes was created by Hermes.
It originates from nature,
lacking the necessary concealment and protection.
It easily gets its users caught up in danger!
But it is also more effective.
And Hermes was developed due to Ancient Hermes' overly dangerous characteristics
and was subsequently improved.
It is particularly important to note that
Hermes and Ancient Hermes
are both important Mystical languages.
They can harness natural forces,
having the capabilities for sacrificial rituals, prayers, and spellcasting.
But, improper use
may awaken certain things that should not exist.
Be careful not to attract the attention of an evil god!
Emperor Roselle once said, "Knowledge is power."
Youngster,
This much is the most fundamental linguistic knowledge of the Mystical World.
Take your time to digest this knowledge.
May the Goddess bless you!