Q Theatre
Divination Club
This here
is our club's newly arrived diviner,
Mr. Moretti!
Very outstanding,
his divinations are very accurate!
So young!
Is that so?
This here gentleman,
today would be unwise for you to go out,
as calamity may descend from the heavens...
What calamity might descend from the heavens?
As expected, he's a charlatan and a fraud.
Precisely.
Only an eight pence divination fee,
how accurate could he possibly be?
I just knew that youngsters were not reliable!
Does this count?
I think it counts.
Yeah.
Who said calamities need to be big?
This master seems pretty accurate.
Yeah.
Master Moretti, please divine for me!
I'd like to try a divination too!
Thank you, Master!
I'm not one to chase after money.
But if I'd known earlier, I'd have set the divination fee a little higher!