Q Theatre
Zhou Mingrui's bad day
I,
Zhou Mingrui,
am an ordinary wage earner.
Today, just as always,
I worked overtime until 10pm.
Right now is 12 at midnight.
I may have reached a turning point in my life.
Master of
Empty-Promises
The new guy touched your code,
the program crashed!
Master of
Empty-Promises
Also, Client A's request
needs to be rolled back to v1.
Master of
Empty-Promises
Clients B and C both bailed,
Master of
Empty-Promises
so no year-end bonus this year.
Master of
Empty-Promises
But in the future...
Master of
Empty-Promises
Yanzi,
don't go!
Life
doesn't change!
Youngster.
Need a phone?
DIVIN-
ATION
Don't go, don't go!
Our meeting here is fate,
I've figured that you're plagued with bad luck.
So this Ritual of Fortune Reversal,
is yours for 10 yuan!
Do you really think I'd fall for something like this?
Master of Empty-Promises
Aiyah! I forgot to remind you, tonight
they're cutting the power! Remember
to save your data! Hee hee (~^ O ^~)
Master of Empty-Promises
Aiyah! I forgot to remind you, tonight
they're cutting the power! Remember
to save your data! Hee hee (~^ O ^~)
I choose the ritual!
Compendium of
Secret  Alchemical Practices
from the
Qin and Han Dynasties
No way it really can...
turn my luck around!
Where is this?!