I
just got here,
so I don't quite understand Mr. Fool yet.
But.
Mr. Fool dared to ignore those terrifying monsters from the depths of darkness,
and pull me from that cursed land.
He must be omnipotent!
Brave and fearless!
It's not
actually haunted, is it?
The Mr. Fool in my heart.
Naturally, is powerful!
On par with gods, powerful!
I'm only Sequence 8!
Don't come over here!
I must apologize first.
I always want to use money as compensation in transactions.
How could a great personage like Mr. Fool
look upon something as tawdry as money?
In short,
the Mr. Fool in my heart
is a transcendent,
wise, and serene elder!
What're you watching?
You're so focused.
Say...
a clown's balance compared to a cat's,
which is better?