Q Theatre
Terminating Lease
Is this our new house?
It feels like I'm dreaming.
Then we don't need to wake up.
But,
there's still our six-month contract on Iron Cross Street.
That stingy landlord isn't going to agree to terminate the lease.
We'll have to pay a hefty penalty for breach of contract.
No need to worry,
Melissa.
Leave it to me!
What!
Terminate the lease?!
I refuse!
Mr. Franky.
Let's not forget, we have a contract!
The penalty for six-months
is one gold pound!
Mr. Franky,
you ought to be earning more!
The rent for the three of us
is five soli and sixpence.
If it were a family of six or seven,
they would certainly be willing to pay more!
Then it'd be nineteen soli!
The rent in Tingen has been rising continuously recently.
1 gold pound = 20 soli
The longer we stay, the more you lose.
Soli
1 gold pound = 20 soli
Eighteeen soli!
I need time to find new tenants!
I believe you could find some within two days!
Actually, if we just sublet,
Soli
we could earn eighteen soli in just six-months!
But we
didn't do it like that.
On the contrary.
We would even compensate you for the loss of these two days.
Just using the deposit we paid―—
three soli!
Benson.
You truly are a conscientious
and upright young man!
Contract Terminated
You're a genius,
Benson!
After all, Mr. Landlord's IQ
isn't even that of a curly-haired baboon.
Soli