Old Neil's Mysticism Class Episode 2
Studious Beyonders,
Old Neil's Mysticism Class
today's mysticism lesson is packed with knowledge.
Pay attention to what you see and hear,
jot down any questions you have,
and wait until everything is over before consulting me.
Old Neil's Mysticism Class
Ah
Do you still remember Dunn inviting Klein to become a Beyonder
and letting him choose a Pathway?
This is exactly the first piece of mysticism knowledge for today's lesson.
Beyonder Pathways
Beyonder Pathways.
Beyonder Pathways are a Beyonder's power system.
Beyonder Pathways
They comprise a total of 22 Pathways,
which can be understood as 22 types of professsions.
Beyonder Pathways
Every Pathway is comprised of different Sequences,
which can be understood as different ranks.
The smaller the Sequence number,
the stronger the corresponding abilities.
Beyonders can drink the corresponding potion
to raise their Sequence level.
And each time their Sequence level advances,
they not only gain new Beyonder abilities
but their existing abilities are also be enhanced.
Additionally, each Sequence
has corresponding acting principles and promotion rituals,
which constrain and guide the growth of those on a Pathway.
Now here's a question,
if you were to become a Beyonder
which Pathway would you chose?
Hahaha
Next, let me introduce the Nighthawks,
which is also the organization I belong to.
The Nighthawks
are affiliated with the Church of the Evernight Goddess.
As an official Beyonder organziation,
they are responsible for handling supernatural incidents within the Loen Kingdom;
confronting evil cults and secret organizations,
and managing one's own risk of losing control brought by potions.
The Tingen Nighthawks squad I belong to
is mainly responsible for Tingen's North Borough,
West Borough, and the Golden Indus Borough, among other areas,
and supernatural incidents related to the followers of the Goddess.
The current official members include Captain Dunn,
Leonard, Frye, Royale,
Kenley, and Seeka.
The civilian staff has me, Rozanne, and Bredt.
as well as the just recently added member of the Nighthawks squad
who is temporarily operating under civilian staff, Klein.
Hahaha, right,
when introducing ourselves to outsiders,
remember to say we're from the Blackthorn Security Company!
Occasionally, we will also take on a few small tasks like
finding lost cats or dogs,
and the money we earn provides quite a bit of extra bonuses!
Next up, I'll begin teaching you the most common,
easiest to grasp,
and most useful ability in the future of mysticism.
Spirit Vision!
Spirit Vision is the ability of Beyonders to use spiritual sensitivity to perceive the spirit world.
The ability to observe a target's aura and Soul Body.
Using Spirit Vision,
you can not only directly see certain spiritual bodies, ghosts, and specters,
but you can also see others' Ether Bodies.
From their thickness, brightness, and color
you can determine their health and emotional state.
If your Spirit Vision improves
or you grasp more mysticism knowledge,
you can even determine the lifespan of others.
The inner layer of the Astral Projection's
corresponding colors represent prevailing emotions.
Red means passion and excitement.
Orange means warmth and satisfaction.
Yellow means happiness and extroversion.
Green means calm and peace.
Blue means coldness and stillness that one is in thought.
White means brightness, an eagerness to improve.
Dark colors mean worry, sorrow, and silence.
Purple means that spirituality is taking control of the lead,
coldness and estrangement...
Smart youngsters,
today's mysticism class will stop right here!
Lastly, I want to leave you with an assignment
to activate your Spirit Vision.
Take a look at what my current emotions are like!